[
  {
    "question": "Unics",
    "answer": "1969",
    "author": "Bell Labs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unix v1",
    "answer": "1971"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unix v2",
    "answer": "1972"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unix v3",
    "answer": "1973"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unix v4",
    "answer": "1973"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unix v5",
    "answer": "1974"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unix v6",
    "answer": "1975"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unix v7",
    "answer": "1979"
  },
  {
    "question": "3BSD",
    "answer": "1979",
    "author": "Berkeley Software Distribution"
  },
  {
    "question": "4.2BSD",
    "answer": "1983"
  },
  {
    "question": "System V",
    "answer": "1983",
    "author": "AT&T & Bell Labs"
  },
  {
    "question": "4.3BSD",
    "answer": "1986"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unix Tahoe",
    "answer": "1988"
  },
  {
    "question": "System V Release 4 (SVR4)",
    "answer": "1988"
  },
  {
    "question": "4.3-Reno (BSD)",
    "answer": "1990"
  },
  {
    "question": "4.4BSD",
    "answer": "1993"
  },
  {
    "question": "Linux 1.0",
    "answer": "1994"
  },
  {
    "question": "386BSD",
    "answer": "1994"
  }
]